A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.28 (A2002) FA489
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2002.017: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2004; AC.2002.017; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.017.1; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RF 95027 #132 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - NATIONAL MUSEUM OF AMERICAN ART - "KALEIDOSCOPE" EXHIBITION, 1995-1997 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95027 #139 - BRONX MUSEUM OF THE ARTS - "BRONX SPACES", 1995-1997 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95027 #140 - CROCKER ART MUSEUM ASSOCIATI ON - EXHIBITION OF CALIFORNIA INDIAN BASKETRY, 1995-1997 (Box R3456)
    - RF 94035 #34; RF 94039 #35 -UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - WORKSHOP ON BURDEN OF DISEASE, 1996-1997 (Box R3457)
    - RF 95027 #142 - VISUAL ARTS RESEARCH AND RESOURCE CENTER RELATING TO THE CARIBBEAN - "TRANSFORMING THE CROWN" EXHIBITION, 1995-2000 (Box R3457)
    - RF 95027 #148 - SPELMAN COLLEGE - EXHIBITION: "BEARING WITNESS: CONTEMPORARY WORK BY AFRICAN AMERICAN WOMEN", 1995-2000 (Box R3457)
    - RF 95035 #23 - INSTITUTE FOR INTERNATIONAL LEADERSHIP - SCHOOL SUPERINTENDENT CANDIDATES, 1990-1998 (Box R3457)
    - RF 95037 #8 - WOOD, TOM - TERMITES AND MAIZE IN EASTERN AND SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1995-1997 (Box R3457)
    - RF 95040 #69 - REDDY, VIJAY - UNDER-REPRESENTATION OF BLACK SOUTH AFRICANS IN RESEARCH IN SCIENCE EDUCATION, 1996-2000 (Box R3457)
    - RF 95040 #70 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - WORKSHOP TO FOLLOW UP THE HARARE GENERATOR, 1996-1997 (Box R3457)
    - RF 95043 #26 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - PAN-AFRICAN MEETING ON PROMOTION OF AFRICAN ARTS AND CULTURE, 1996-1997 (Box R3457)
    - RF 95043 #27 - FILM TV MARKET INITIATIVE (SOUTH AFRICA) - AFRICAN PARTICIPATION IN FIRST SOUTHERN AFRICAN FILM TELEVISION MARKET, 1996-1997 (Box R3457)
    - RF 95043 #32 - THAPONG INTERNATIONAL ARTISTS' WORKSHOP (BOTSWANA) - 1996 WORKSHOP, 1996-1997 (Box R3457)
    - RF 95043 #33 - (Strengthening African Cultural Institutions) - Meeting of Steering Committee of Pan-African Festival of Arts and Culture, 1996-1997 (Box R3457)
    - RF 95046 #9 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - INTERNATIONAL BIOSAFETY WORKSHOP, 1997-1998 (Box R3458)
    - RF 95047 #40 - ASSOCIATION FOR REPRODUCTIVE AND FAMILY HEALTH (NIGERIA) - WEST AFRICAN YOUTH INITIATIVE, 1991-2000 (Box R3458)
    - RF 95050 #88 - ERINOSHO, STELLA YEMISI - SECONDARY SCHOOL CURRICULUM MATERIALS IN NIGERIA, 1996-1997 (Box R3458)
    - RF 95052 #90 - HENSON FOUNDATION - 1996 INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL OF PUPPET THEATER, 1995-1998 (Box R3458)
    - RF 95052 #92 - ALTERNATE ROOTS - TWENTIETH ANNIVERSARY ACTIVITIES, 1996-1997 (Box R3458)
    - RF 95052 #93 - JACOB'S PILLOW - 1997 FESTIVAL SEASON, 1996-1997 (Box R3458)
    - RF 95052 #94 - BANG ON A CAN - 10TH ANNIVERSARY BANG ON A CAN FESTIVAL SEASON, 1996-1997 (Box R3458)
    - RF 95052 #95 - SPOLETO FESTIVAL USA - 1997 FESTIVAL SEASON, 1996-1998 (Box R3458)
    - RF 95052 #96 - NEW 42ND STREET - PROGRAMMING ACTIVITIES FOR NEW VICTORY THEATER'S INAUGURAL SEASON, 1995-1998 (Box R3459)
    - RF 95053 #2 - NATIONAL HUMANITIES CENTER - IMPLICATIONS OF NEW INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES, 1995-1999 (Box R3459)
    - RF 95054 #27 - SAN FRANCISCO MIME TROUPE - ORIGINAL MUSICAL COMEDY BY YOUTH, 1995-1997. 2000 (Box R3459)
    - RF 95055 #2 - NEW ENGLAND FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - ARTS AND CULTURAL INDICATORS IN CIVIC LIFE, 1995-2000 (Box R3459)
    - RF 95056 #7 - PACIFIC AMERICAN COMMUNITY FOUNDATION - SAN DIEGO/TIJUANA BORDER COMMUNITY PROJECT, 1996-1997 (Box R3459)
    - RF 95056 #8 - TRINITY UNIVERSITY - YOUTH AND PUBLIC SCHOOL EDUCATION ISSUES IN SAN ANTONIO, 1995-1998 (Box R3459)
    - RF 95056 #9 - ACCESS TUCSON - COMMUNITY DIALOGUE AND PROBLEM SOLVING IN TUCSON, 1995-1997 (Box R3459)
    - RF 95059 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - NATIONWIDE NETWORK OF COMMUNITY-BUILDING INITIATIVES, 1995-1998 (Box R3459)
- AC.2002.040: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2001; AC.2002.040; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.040.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 95061 #2 - BARNARD COLLEGE - PRIVATE-SECTOR JOBS AND CITY-OWNED HOUSING FOR SALE TO PRIVATE ENTREPRENEURS, 1994-2000 (Box R3460)
    - RF 95062 #80 - RAVENSWOOD CITY SCHOOL DISTRICT - BAY AREA SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1996-1997 (Box R3460)
    - RF 95062 #81 - SAN FRANCISCO UNIFIED SCHOOL DISTRICT - BAY AREA SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1997-1998 (Box R3460)
    - RF 95062 #82 - OAKLAND UNIFIED SCHOOL DISTRICT - BAY AREA SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1996-1997 (Box R3460)
    - RF 96001 #403 - JOHN INNES INSTITUTE - RICE TUNGRO VIRUS, 1985-1998 (Box R3460)
    - RF 96001 #427 - SWISS FEDERAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - TRANSGENIC RICE, 1996-1999 (Box R3460)
    - RF 96001 #430 - KANSAS STATE UNIVERSITY - RICE, 1985-1998 (Box R3460)
    - RF 96001 #436 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (THAILAND) - THIRD ASIA-PACI FIC CONFERENCE ON AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1995-1999 (Box R3460)
    - RF 96001 #438 - CENTRAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR FOOD CROPS - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY UNIT, 1998-1999 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #439 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - MOLECULAR GENETIC ANALYSIS OF BLAST RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1995-1998 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #445 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - INSTITUTE OF GENETICS - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR DAI SHUNHONG, 1996-1998 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #446 - THAI RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (THAILAND) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR KANCHANA KLAKHAENG, 1995-1998 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #447 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY PROGRAM REGIONAL MEETING, 1996-1999 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #448 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - AGROBACTERI UM-BASED VECTOR CONSTRUCTION AND RICE, 1996-1998 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #450 - FRENCH INSTITUTE OF SCIENTIFIC RESEARCH FOR COOPERATIVE DEVELOPMENT (ORSTOM) (FRANCE) - ESTABLISH A RICE TRANSFORMATION TRAINING CENTER, 1994-1999 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #459 - CUU LONG DELTA RICE RESEARCH (VIETNAM) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR BUI CHI BUU, 1995-1998 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #472 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - INTERNATIONAL RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY PROGRAM REGIONAL MEETING, 1996-1999 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #481 - RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (THAILAND) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR KINGKARN PITCHAYAKUN, 1996-1998 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #483 - OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY - INTERNATIONAL, INTERACTIVE RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY ELECTRONIC NETWORK (RBNET), 1992-1997 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #485 - WEST AFRICA RICE DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATION (IVORY COAST) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR SEMON MANDE, 1996-1998 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #489 - ZHEJIANG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR FU XIANGDONG, 1995-1999 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #490 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR CAO MENGLIANG, 1996-2001 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #492 - AGRICULTURAL GENETICS INSTITUTE (VIETNAM) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR LUU THI NGOC HUYEN, 1996-1998 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #500 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - REGIONAL MEETING IN NEW DELHI OF THE INTERNATIONAL RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY PROGRAM, 1995-2000 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96001 #505 - UNIVERSITY OF HYDERABAD (INDIA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR GANDIKOTA MADHURI, 1996-1998 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96005 #102 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY - INSTITUTE OF ENVIRONMENT AND NATURAL RESOURCES (UGANDA) - AFRICAN HIGHLANDS INITIATIVE, 1996-2000 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96005 #103 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - AMERICAN SOCIETY OF AGRONOMY MEETINGS, 1996-2000 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96005 #93 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - SYMPOSIUM ON CARBON AND NUTRIENT DYNAMICS IN ECOSYSTEMS, 1995-2000 (Box R3461)
    - RF 96007 #28 - MURANGA, FLORENCE - BANANA STARCH PHYSICOCHEMICAL PROPERTIES, 1995-2000 (Box R3461)
    - RF 95027 #145; RF 96015 #146 - BROOKLYN HISTORICAL SOCIETY -. EXHIBITIONS AND PUBLICATIONS ON CHINESEAMERICAN COMMUNITY IN SUNSET PARK, BROOKLYN, 1996-1997 (Box R3462)
    - RF 96011 #113 - ASIAN FORUM OF PARLIAMENTARIANS ON POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT (THAILAND) - VISIT REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH AND FAMILY PLANNING CENTERS, 1996-1998 (Box R3462)
    - RF 96011 #82 - INTERNATIONAL UNION FOR THE SCIENTIFIC STUDY OF POPULATION (BELGIUM) - SEMINARS ON THE FERTILITY TRANSITION IN SOUTH ASIA AND FEMALE EMPOWERMENT AND DEMOGRAPHIC ANALYSIS, 1996-1998 (Box R3462)
    - RF 96011 #87 - EAST-WEST CENTER - CONFERENCE AND PUBLICATION ON STATUS OF WOMEN AND DEMOGRAPHIC CHANGE, 1994-1997 (Box R3462)
    - RF 96011 #96 - PLANET 21 (ENGLAND) - SPECIAL ISSUE OF PEOPLE AND THE PLANET MAGAZINE, 1996-1998 (Box R3462)
    - RF 96011 #98 - WOMEN'S ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT ORGANIZATION - REPRESENTING WOMEN'S REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH INTERESTS, 1996-1998 (Box R3462)
    - RF 96015 #151 - MUSEUM OF PHOTOGRAPHIC ARTS - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1995-1998 (Box R3462)
    - RF 96015 #152 - MUSEUM FOR AFRICAN ART - "ART OF THE BAGA" EXHIBITION, 1995-1997 (Box R3462)
    - RF 96015 #154 - ASIA SOCIETY - EXHIBITION, "TRADITIONS/TENSIONS: CONTEMPORARY ART IN ASIA", 1996-1998 (Box R3462)
    - RF 96015 #155 - FIELD MUSEUM OF NATURAL HISTORY - "LIVING TOGETHER" PUBLIC LEARNING PROGRAM, 1996-1999 (Box R3462)
    - RF 96015 #156 - OAKLAND MUSEUM/MUSEUM OF CALIFORNIA FOUNDATION - EXHIBITION ON CALIFORNIA GOLD RUSH, 1995-1998 (Box R3462)
    - RF 96015 #157 - INSTALLATION GALLERY - "INSITE 97", 1996-2000 (Box R3462)
    - RF 95024 #265; RF 96024 #266 - DIVERSE WORKS - THEATER WORK INVOLVING HIV POSITIVE LATINAS IN HOUSTON, 1996-1997 (Box R3463)
    - RF 96015 #158 - INSTITUTE OF CONTEMPORARY ART - EXHIBITION, "NEW HISTORIES", 1996-1997 (Box R3463)
    - RF 96015 #159 - YALE UNIVERSITY - EXHIBITION "BAULE: AFRICAN ART/WESTERN EYES", 1996-1999 (Box R3463)
    - RF 96015 #160 - JAPANESE AMERICAN NATIONAL MUSEUM - NATIONAL PARTNERSHIP PROGRAM, 1993-1998 (Box R3463)
    - RF 96015 #161 - PEABODY MUSEUM OF SALEM AND ESSEX INSTITUTE - EXHIBITION, "GIFTS OF THE SPIRIT", 1996-2000 (Box R3463)
    - RF 96015 #162 - SELF-HELP GRAPHICS AND ARTS, INC. - PROGRAM ACTIVITIES, 1994-2000 (Box R3463)
    - RF 96020 #59 - ALBERT SZENT-GYORGI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY (HUNGARY) - SYMPOSIUM ON POST-OVULATORY AND POST-COITAL CONTRACEPTION, 1996-1997 (Box R3463)
    - RF 96023 #263 - PROGRAM FOR ART ON FILM - EXPAND WEB SITE, 1997-1998 (Box R3463)
    - RF 96024 #267 - DONALD BYRD DANCE FOUNDATION - "JAZZ TRAIN" DANCE WORK, 1997-1999 (Box R3463)
- AC.2002.043: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-2002; AC.2002.043; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.043.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 96024 #268 - EAST BAY CENTER FOR THE PERFORMING ARTS - "DEAI" CONCERT DUET, 1997-1998 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #269 - FOUNDATION FOR DANCE PROMOTION - "THE LOUD BOY", 1996-1998 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #270 - FOUNDATION FOR INDEPENDENT ARTISTS - NEW DANCE WORK BY CHOREOGRAPHERS EIKO AND KOMA OTAKE, 1996-1999 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #271 - FRIENDS OF THE DAVIS CENTER - OPERA, "THE RETURN OF ELIJAH, THE AFRICAN", 1996-1998 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #272 - GREATER TRENTON SYMPHONY ASSOCIATI ON - ORCHESTRA TRILOGY, "THE WHITMAN TRIPTYCH", 1996-1999 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #273 - H.T. DANCE CO. - "TRANSPARENT HINGES", 1996-1999 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #274 - HEART OF THE BEAST THEATRE - PUPPET AND MASK EVENT, "SONG FOR A MILLENIUM", 1996-1998 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #275 - HELENA PRESENTS - POETRY PERFORMANCE WORK ABOUT U.S.-BASED LATINO CULTURES, 1996-1999 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #276 - KRONOS PERFORMING ARTS ASSOCIATION - "ALTAR DE MUERTOS", 1996-1998 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #277 - LINES CONTEMPORARY BALLET - NEW BALLET FOR 15TH ANNIVERSARY, 1996-1997 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #278 - MABOU MINES DEVELOPMENT FOUNDATION - HISTORY OF BELEN, 1996-1999 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #279 - MIAMI LIGHT PROJECT - MULTlMEDIA WORK, "DRUMMIN", 1996-1997 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #280 - MUSICAL TRADITIONS - MUSIC THEATER PRODUCTION, "THE STRANGE, LAST VOYAGE OF DONALD CROWHURST", 1996-1999 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #282 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - "THE REALISM OF SIMPLE MACHINES", 1996-1999 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #283 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - MULTl-MEDIA PERFORMANCE, "AFTER EROS", 1996-1999 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #285 - PICK-UP PERFORMANCE CO. - DANCE/THEATER WORK, "SILENT MOVIE", 1996-1998 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #287 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (BERKELEY) - MUSICAL WORK "WHEN SORROW TURNS TO JOY", 1996-1998 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #288 - REICH MUSIC FOUNDATION - "THREE TALES" MUSICNIDEO/THEATRE WORK, 1996-1999 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #289 - SAN FRANCISCO MIME TROUP - MULTl-MEDIA MUSICAL, "13 DIAS/13 DAYS", 1997 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #291 - THEATER ARTAUD - DANCE/THEATER WORK, "TAKE ME TO THE TENDERLOIN, NOW", 1997-1999 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #293 - TOUCHSTONE THEATRE - CULTURAL EXCHANGE PROJECT, 1996-1999 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #294 - WASHINGTON DRAMA SOCIETY - "PRESS AND THE PRESIDENCY " THEATRICAL EXPLORATION, 1996-1998 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #295 - WORLD MUSIC INSTITUTE - MUSICAL COLLABORATION, "GIVING NEW LIFE TO A DYING HERITAGE", 1996-1998 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #296 - YALE UNIVERSITY - "GEOGRAPHY" DANCE WORK, 1997-1998 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96024 #297 - YARA ARTS GROUP - MUSIC THEATRE WORK, "VIRTUAL SOUNDS", 1996-1998 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96026 #5 - MASSACHUSETTS - LABOR AND WORKFORCE DEVELOPMENT (DEPT. OF) - ONE-STOP CAREER CENTERS, 1996-2001 (Box R3464)
    - RF 96026 #15 - URBAN ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION - ROUNDTABLE DISCUSSION FOR THE SAN FRANCISCO BAYVIEW-HUNTERS POINT DISTRICT, 1997-2001 (Box R3465)
    - RF 96034 #116 - AMERICAN FOUNDATION FOR AIDS RESEARCH - CONFERENCE ON HIV TRANSMISSION FROM MOTHER TO INFANTS, 1997-1998 (Box R3465)
    - RF 96034 #118 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF PREVENTIVE MEDICINE (CHINA) - WORKSHOP ON "INTERVENTION OF HIV/AIDS IN CHINA", 1997-1998 (Box R3465)
    - RF 96035 #505 - XAVIER PONTIFICAL UNIVERSITY (COLOMBIA) - KANGAROO MOTHER INTERVENTION METHOD, 1994-2000 (Box R3465)
    - RF 96035 #506 - UNIVERSITY OF NEWCASTLE (AUSTRALIA) - SOCIAL SCIENCES TRAINING IN INCLEN, 1987-1997 (Box R3465)
    - RF 96035 #507 - NATIONAL FOUNDATION FOR THE CENTERS FOR DISEASE CONTROL AND PREVENTION - PARTICIPATION AT INCLEN XIV MEETING, 1997 (Box R3465)
    - RF 96035 #509 - WEST CHINA UNIVERSITY OF MEDICAL SCIENCES - WORKSHOP FOR CHINESE MEDICAL JOURNAL CHIEF EDITORS, 1996-1998 (Box R3465)
    - RF 96036 #52 - TANZANIA PUBLIC HEALTH ASSOCIATION - EIGHTH INTERNATIONAL CONGRESS, 1996-1998 (Box R3465)
    - RF 96049 #119 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - LEAD PROGRAM IN SOUTH EAST ASIA, 1996-2000 (Box R3465)
    - RF 96060 - NAACP LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND - PROGRAM RESERVE FUND AND LITIGATION ACTIVITY, 1996-1999 (Box R3465)
    - RF 96061 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL AND ECONOMIC STUDIES - CORE SUPPORT FOR ITS POLICY ANALYSIS UNIT, 1994-1998 (Box R3465)
    - RF 96061 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL AND ECONOMIC STUDIES - CORE SUPPORT FOR ITS POLICY ANALYSIS UNIT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1998 (Box R3466, Box R3465, Box R3467)
    - RF 96065 #12 - ACCESS TUCSON - YOUTH AND ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT OF COMMUNITY ACTION NETWORK, 1995-1998 (Box R3467)
    - RF 97001 #532 - MOHAN, MADAN - MAP-BASED GENE CLONING OF GALL MIDGE-RESISTANT GENES, 1991-1998 (Box R3467)
    - RF 97001 #542 - AGRICULTURE RESEARCH ORGANIZATION (ISRAEL) - RICE PRODUCTIVITY AND DROUGHT STRESS, 1997-2002 (Box R3467)
    - RF 97001 #571 - AGRICULTURAL GENETICS INSTITUTE (VIETNAM) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR PHAN TO PHUONG, 1996-1998 (Box R3467)
    - RF 97002 #120 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - WORKSHOP ON AGRICULTURAL SUSTAINABILITY IN AFRICA, 1996-2001 (Box R3467)
    - RF 97002 #121 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - WORKSHOP ON GREEN MANURE AND COVER CROPS, 1997-2000 (Box R3467)
    - RF 96-11 #117; RF 97012 #119 - UNIVERSITY OF HAWAII - POPULATION DYNAMICS AND ECONOMIC GROWTH IN EAST ASIA (MANOA), 1997-1998 (Box R3468)
    - RF 97009 #3 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME'S INTERNATIONAL COLLOQUIUM OF MAYORS, 1997-1998 (Box R3468)
    - RF 97016 #171 - BUFFALO BILL MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION - EXHIBITION, "POWERFUL IMAGES: PORTRAYALS OF NATIVE AMERICA", 1995-1998 (Box R3468)
    - RF 97026 #2 - CENTER FOR NEIGHBORHOOD TECHNOLOGY - FORUMS FOR COOPERATION WITHIN METROPOLITAN REGIONS, 1997 (Box R3468)
- AC.2002.051: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1985-2004; AC.2002.051
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2002.051.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 94-8010-27 - QUEENS COLLEGE - EXHIBITION, "ASIA/AMERICA: IDENTITIES IN CONTEMPORARY ASIAN AMERICAN ART", 1994-1998 (Box R3469)
    - 94-8010-37 - NATIONAL VIDEO RESOURCES - NEW TECHNOLOGIES AND THE PUBLIC SECTOR, 1994-1999 (Box R3469)
    - AH 9448 - NEW SCHOOL FOR SOCIAL RESEARCH - CULTURAL AND POLITICAL CONSEQUENCES OF IMMIGRATION, 1994-1998 (Box R3469)
    - AH 9451 - WORLD CONFERENCE ON RELIGION AND PEACE - SOUTH AFRICA CHAPTER - CONSULTATION ON RELIGIOUS RESPONSE TO "TRUTH AND RECONCILIATION COMMISSION", 1994-1999 (Box R3469)
    - AH 9454 - LIFE AND PEACE INSTITUTE (SWEDEN) - CHURCHES AND TRANSITION TO DEMOCRACY, 1994-1999 (Box R3469)
    - AH 9540 - CAMBODIAN NETWORK COUNCIL - CAMBODIAN ARTIST MENTORING PROJECT, 1994-1998 (Box R3469)
    - AH 9613 - CHINESE UNIVERSITY OF HONG KONG - NEW CULTURAL IMAGINARIES PROJECT, 1996-1998 (Box R3470)
    - AH 9620 - AMERICAN SOCIAL HISTORY PRODUCTIONS - CD-ROM BASED ON "WHO BUILT AMERICA", 1994-2001 (Box R3470)
    - AH 9620 - AMERICAN SOCIAL HISTORY PRODUCTIONS - CD-ROM BASED ON "WHO BUILT AMERICA", PART II - DIGITAL, 1994-2001; 2002:051:001; Digital (Item 2002:051:001)
    - AH 9620 - AMERICAN SOCIAL HISTORY PRODUCTIONS - CD-ROM BASED ON "WHO BUILT AMERICA", PART II - DIGITAL, 1994-2001; 2002:051:002; Digital (Item 2002:051:002)
    - AH 9621 - GUGGENHEIM FOUNDATION - PLAY: "THE BEATIFICATION OF AREA BOY", 1995-1997 (Box R3470)
    - AH 9703 - AMERICAN MUSEUM OF NATURAL HISTORY - CONFERENCE, "CONSTRUCTING CULTURES THEN AND NOW", 1996-1998 (Box R3470)
    - AH 9704 - WORLD ENCYCLOPEDIA OF CONTEMPORARY THEATRE (CANADA) - CONTEMPORARY WORLD THEATER ENCYCLOPEDIA, 1995-1998 (Box R3470)
    - AH 9705 - AMERICAN COMPOSERS FORUM - NEW MUSIC FOR DIVERSE COMMUNITIES, 1996-2001 (Box R3470)
    - AH 9706 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (BERKELEY) - WORKSHOP ON ORAL TRADITIONS OF NORTH PACIFIC RIM, 1996-1998 (Box R3470)
    - AH 9709 - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF LATINO ARTS AND CULTURE - SURVEY AND ASSESSMENT OF U.S. LATINO ORGANIZATIONS, 1997-2000 (Box R3470)
    - AH 9710 - GERTRUDE STEIN REPERTORY THEATRE - DIGITAL NETWORKING PROJECT, 1997-1998 (Box R3470)
    - RF 96015 #163; AH 9701 - NATIONAL GALLERY OF ART - EXHIBITION, "MILLENNIUM OF GLORY: SCULPTURE OF CAMBODIA", 1996-1997 (Box R3470)
    - AH 9714 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE, "YARI YARI, BLACK WOMEN WRITERS AND THE FUTURE", 1996-1999 (Box R3471)
    - AH 9716 - DARTMOUTH COLLEGE - BLACK THEATRE SUMMIT, "ON GOLDEN POND", 1997-1998 (Box R3471)
    - AH 9717 - SNUG HARBOR CULTURAL CENTER - SERVE DIVERSE COMMUNITIES OF STATEN ISLAND, 1997-1999 (Box R3471)
    - AH 9720 - AMERICAN ASSOCIATION OF MUSEUMS - FORUM ON MUSEUMS AND SUSTAINABLE COMMUNITIES OF THE AMERICAS, 1997-1999 (Box R3471)
    - AH 9721 - FOUNDRY THEATRE - CONFERENCE/PERFORMANCE, "A CONVERSATION ON HOPE", 1997-1998 (Box R3471)
    - AH 9723 - ASSOCIATION FOR CULTURAL EQUITY - ALAN LOMAX FIELD RECORDINGS, 1997-1999 (Box R3471)
    - AH 9801 - NETWORK OF CULTURAL CENTERS OF COLOR - IMPLEMENTATION OF BUSINESS PLAN, 1997-1999; 2004 (Box R3471)
    - AH 9805 - VIVIAN BEAUMONT THEATER - AFRICAN THEATER PROJECT OF 1998 DIRECTORS LAB (Box R3471)
    - AH 9818 - JACOB'S PILLOW DANCE FESTIVAL - LEADERSHIP FORUM ON PRESENTING INTERNATIONAL WORK, 1998 (Box R3471)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS), AC.2002.051.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - AS 9431 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - "STRENGTHENING REGIONAL NETWORKS FOR POLICY RESEARCH ON THE LATIN AMERICAN HILLSIDES", 1994-1998 (Box R3471)
    - AS 9438 - YALE UNIVERSITY - INTRODUCING TRANSGENES INTO APHID SYMBIOTIC BACTERIA, 1993-1999 (Box R3471)
    - AS 9532 - FUDAN UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - INSECT VECTOR COMPETENCE AND RICE DISEASE, 1995-2000 (Box R3471)
    - AS 9609 - AGRICULTURAL EXTENSION IN ZIMBABWE, 1991-2000 (Box R3471)
    - AS 9142 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRl-BIOTECH APPLICATIONS - AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY TRANSFER, 1992-1999 (Box R3471)
    - AS 9618 - NYANAPAH, JAMES O. - DISEASE RESISTANCE IN TROPICAL MAIZE, 1995-2000 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9621 - PURDUE UNIVERSITY - GENOTYPJC DIVERSITY INDEXING, 1989-1999 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9708 - HERNANDEZ DAUMAS, SALVADOR - AGROFORESTRY SYSTEM APPROPRIATE FOR TROPICAL GRASS IN MEXICO, 1996-1999 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9709 - WAGENINGEN AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (NETHERLANDS) - WORKSHOP AND BOOK ON WILDLIFE IN AFRICA, 1996-1999 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9711 - INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT AND EDUCATION IN AGRICULTURE AND LIFE SCIENCES, INC. - AGRICULTURE IN CHINA MONOGRAPH, 1997-1998 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9712 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - SYMPOSIUM ON HETEROSIS IN CROPS, 1996-1999 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9715 - MILLENNIUM INSTITUTE - CHINESE AND GLOBAL FOOD SECURITY, 1997-2000 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9717 - PROJECTO SIERRA SANTA MARTA (MEXICO) - WORKSHOP ON PEST AND DISEASE CONTROL OF MAIZE AND OTHER CROPS, 1997-1999 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9721 - NJERU, GEOFFREY R. - TECHNICAL CHANGE AND ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL-SCALE FARMERS IN EASTERN KENYA, 1996-1999 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9723 - TEXAS A, 1997-2000 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9726 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - LAIKIPIA RESEARCH PROJECT, 1997-2000 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9727 - TATA INSTITUTE OF FUNDAMENTAL RESEARCH (INDIA) - WORKSHOP ON PLANT DEVELOPMENT, 1997-1999 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9807 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME - WORKSHOP ON SOIL BIOLOGY, 1997-1999 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9815 - NEW SCHOOL UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE - FOOD: NATURE AND CULTURE, 1997-2001 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9817 - YOUTH FOR ACTION (INDIA) - WORKSHOP ON SUSTAINABLE RESOURCE MANAGEMENT, 1998 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9819 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - MICROECONOMICS COURSE IN THE PH.D. PROGRAM, 1998 (Box R3472)
    - AS 9824 - PURDUE UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP ON WEST AFRICA HYBRID SEED, 1998-1999 (Box R3472)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2002.051.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - EO 8519 - NATIONAL SENIOR CITIZENS LAW CENTER - WOMEN AND PENSIONS, 1985-1990 (Box R3472)
    - EO 9235 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUESETTS - "EMPLOYERS, HIRING AND URBAN INEQUALITY: A MULTI-CITY STUDY" (LOWELL), 1992-1997 (Box R3472)
- AC.2002.053: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2002; AC.2002.053; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2002.053.1; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - EO 9513 - CENTER ON BUDGET AND POLICY PRIORITIES - STATE FISCAL PROJECT'S WORK ON BALANCED BUDGET, 1994-1999 (Box R3473)
    - EO 9531 - NATIONAL URBAN LEAGUE - ECONOMIC SELF-SUFFICIENCY OF URBAN POOR, 1994-1999 (Box R3473)
    - EO 9531 - NATIONAL URBAN LEAGUE - ECONOMIC SELF-SUFFICIENCY OF URBAN POOR - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1999 (Box R3473)
    - EO 9607 - RESEARCH FOUNDATION OF STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - NEIGHBORHOODS THAT HAVE BEATEN ODDS AGAINST DECAY, 1994-1998 (Box R3473)
    - EO 9609 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA AT CHAPEL HILL - URBAN INVESTMENT STRATEGIES CENTER, 1994-1998 (Box R3473)
    - EO 9619 - DEVELOPMENT TRAINING INSTITUTE - COMMUNITY BUILDING AND GRANTMAKING POLICY, 1995-1998 (Box R3474)